

Farhan Elly Alkatiri

Jalan Langgar No. 12, Jakarta +6287842302725 Farhanalktr91@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/farhanalktr

Website developer who uses JavaScript to create applications with the added help of the ReactJS library as well as Tailwind and Boostrap to speed up the design process on websites. Want to continue gaining experience and willing to learn and deepen knowledge about website development to help companies manage or create applications.

Educational Background

UIN Syarifhidayatullah Jakarta

System Information

Graduated with GPA 3.38 out of 4.00

14 Senior High School

Majoring in science program

Skills & Proficiencies

- JavaScript
- React JS
- Tailwind
- Boostrap
- Git
- Microsoft Office
- · Problem Solving
- Case Analysis
- UI Design
- Ux Research

Language

- Indonesia
- English

Portofolio

https://farhanalktr.vercel.app/

Work Experience

Admin Marketing

PT Panasonic Gobel Cawang *May 2021 to October 2022*

- Managedata from the implementation of marketing programs related to customers.
- Provide solutions to customers, if there are errors or complaints related to marketing programs.
- Coordinate customer data that has met the criteria to get prizes from marketing programs.

Organizations

Himpunan Mahasiswa Sistem Informasi (HIMSI)

Head of communications

2021-2022

- Maintain friendly relations with off-campus organizations.
- Create events in collaboration with external parties, such as Blood Donation events.
- Establish cooperative relationships with other campuses.

Certification

Complete UI Designer: Visual Design, Prototype, Usability Testing

The training was held by BuildwithAngga in 2022

Complete Web & Mobile Designer: UI/UX, Figma, + more

The training was held by Udemy in 2022

Organizations

Ikatan Mahasiswa Sistem Informasi (IMSII)

Coordinator of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of the IMSII Region

2020-2021

- Become a policy information coordinator for central programs to several campuses in certain areas.
- Manage project information from various campuses in the relevant area.

Head of the IMSII Public Relations division for the Jabodetabek region

2021-2022

• Coordinate various campuses in collecting company data.